Preliminary Inventory to the Harry Fleischman Papers TAM.115
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series II: Photographs and Ephemera, 1905-1989
  - Harry Fleischman: Portraits, 1955-1977, undated (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Labor Exhibits and Displays, undated (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous Ephemera (Oversize), undated (Box Shared Tamiment XOS003, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous Photographs, late 1930s - 1978 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Negatives, undated (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Negatives [Poor Condition], undated (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Norman Thomas: Ephemera, 1982-1983, undated (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Norman Thomas: Graphics, 1948-1978 (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Norman Thomas: Oversize Photographs (I), 1926-1959 (Box Shared Tamiment XOS003, Folder 2)
  - Norman Thomas: Oversize Photographs (II), 1926-1959 (Box Shared Tamiment XOS003, Folder 3)
  - Norman Thomas: Photo Album, 1926-1980 (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - Norman Thomas: Photo Album "As A Young Man", 1905, undated (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - Norman Thomas: Round-the-World Trip, 1907 (Box 39, Folder 16)
  - Norman Thomas: Round-the-World Trip (Postcards), 1907 (Box 39, Folder 17)
  - Norman Thomas and Family (I), 1906-1981, undated (Box 39, Folder 18)
  - Norman Thomas and Family (II), 1906-1981, undated (Box 39, Folder 19)
  - Norman Thomas High School Celebration, 1977 (Box 39, Folder 20)
  - Norman Thomas High School Dedication, 1976 (Box 39, Folder 21)
  - Norman Thomas High School Photo Album, 1982 (Box Shared Tamiment OS008, Folder 1)
  - Oversize Photographs and Displays, 1936-1968 (Flat-file-folder 1)
  - Portraits (Miscellaneous), early 1940s-1954, undated (Box 39, Folder 22)
  - Slides, undated (Box 39, Folder 23)
  - Stickers, 1983 (Box 39, Folder 24)
  - Unidentified Photo Album, undated (Box 39, Folder 25)
  - Unidentified Events, 1960, undated (Box 39, Folder 26)
  - United Press International Photos (Used), 1941-1965, undated (Box 39, Folder 27)
  - Young People's Socialist League Armbands, undated (Box 39, Folder 28)
  - Workers: On the Job, undated (Box 39, Folder 29)
  - Workers: Striking, undated (Box 39, Folder 30)
  - Workers: Summer School, 1948-1955 (Box 39, Folder 31)